[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_container_00_FQ_01",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Perronelle",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FishQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_FishingPole_FishQuestT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_container_00_FQ_02",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Perronelle",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FishQ_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C91_FishQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_02_Vector",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_FQ_02_Vector_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Khadijah",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FQ_02_Vector",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C91_FishQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_02_Vector_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_container_00_FQ_03",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Khadijah",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FishQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C91_FQ_02_Vector",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_03_Vector",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_FQ_03_Vector_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Ishikawa",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FQ_03_Vector",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C91_FishQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_03_Vector_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_container_00_FQ_04",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Ishikawa",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FishQ_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C91_FQ_03_Vector",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "BaitFishT3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_container_00_FQ_05",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Ishikawa",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FishQ_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C91_FishQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_05_Vector",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_FQ_05_Vector_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Khadijah",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FQ_05_Vector",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C91_FishQ_05",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_05_Vector_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_06_RotsHead",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_container_00_FQ_06",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Khadijah",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FishQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C91_FQ_05_Vector",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_RotsHead_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_06_Vector",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_FQ_06_Vector_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Perronelle_C",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FQ_06_Vector",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C91_FishQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_06_Vector_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_container_00_FQ_07",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Pelles_A",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FishQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C91_FQ_06_Vector",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C91_FQ_08_FisherKing",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"Task": "C91_container_00_FQ_08",
		"NpcDestinationId": "Fish_Perronelle_C",
		"AchievementId": "C91_FishQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C91_FishQ_07",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_title",
		"Description": "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_complete",
		"QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
	}
]